{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Solar Water Heater Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40359/":{"taskOID":40359,"originalTaskOID":40359,"setID":653,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6180,"questionDisplayText":"Problem Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you need service? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7982,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"No hot water","answerDisplayText":"No hot water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Need Maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Need Maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8003,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"System leaks","answerDisplayText":"System leaks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8004,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Pump problem","answerDisplayText":"Pump problem","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8005,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Making noise","answerDisplayText":"Making noise","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8006,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Controller problem","answerDisplayText":"Controller problem","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8007,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Runs after dark","answerDisplayText":"Runs after dark","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8008,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Damaged solar collectors","answerDisplayText":"Damaged solar collectors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6181,"questionDisplayText":"Type of heater","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of solar water heater do you have? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8010,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Active","answerDisplayText":"Active","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8011,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Passive","answerDisplayText":"Passive","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8012,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Thermosiphon","answerDisplayText":"Thermosiphon","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8013,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Batch","answerDisplayText":"Batch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8014,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Household water used in system (Direct)","answerDisplayText":"Household water used in system (Direct)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8015,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Heat transfer fluid in system (Indirect)","answerDisplayText":"Heat transfer fluid in system (Indirect)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8016,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6182,"questionDisplayText":"Size of water heater being replaced.","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the size of your current water heater?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8017,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"30 Gallons","answerDisplayText":"30 Gallons","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8018,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"50 Gallons","answerDisplayText":"50 Gallons","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8019,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"40 Gallons","answerDisplayText":"40 Gallons","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8020,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6180,"questionDisplayText":"Problem Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you need service? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7982,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"No hot water","answerDisplayText":"No hot water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Need Maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Need Maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8003,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"System leaks","answerDisplayText":"System leaks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8004,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Pump problem","answerDisplayText":"Pump problem","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8005,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Making noise","answerDisplayText":"Making noise","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8006,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Controller problem","answerDisplayText":"Controller problem","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8007,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Runs after dark","answerDisplayText":"Runs after dark","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8008,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Damaged solar collectors","answerDisplayText":"Damaged solar collectors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":7982,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"No hot water","answerDisplayText":"No hot water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Need Maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Need Maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8003,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"System leaks","answerDisplayText":"System leaks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8004,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Pump problem","answerDisplayText":"Pump problem","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8005,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Making noise","answerDisplayText":"Making noise","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8006,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Controller problem","answerDisplayText":"Controller problem","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8007,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Runs after dark","answerDisplayText":"Runs after dark","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8008,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Damaged solar collectors","answerDisplayText":"Damaged solar collectors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6181,"questionDisplayText":"Type of heater","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of solar water heater do you have? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8010,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Active","answerDisplayText":"Active","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8011,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Passive","answerDisplayText":"Passive","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8012,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Thermosiphon","answerDisplayText":"Thermosiphon","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8013,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Batch","answerDisplayText":"Batch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8014,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Household water used in system (Direct)","answerDisplayText":"Household water used in system (Direct)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8015,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Heat transfer fluid in system (Indirect)","answerDisplayText":"Heat transfer fluid in system (Indirect)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8016,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8010,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Active","answerDisplayText":"Active","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8011,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Passive","answerDisplayText":"Passive","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8012,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Thermosiphon","answerDisplayText":"Thermosiphon","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8013,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Batch","answerDisplayText":"Batch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8014,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Household water used in system (Direct)","answerDisplayText":"Household water used in system (Direct)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8015,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Heat transfer fluid in system (Indirect)","answerDisplayText":"Heat transfer fluid in system (Indirect)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8016,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6182,"questionDisplayText":"Size of water heater being replaced.","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the size of your current water heater?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8017,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"30 Gallons","answerDisplayText":"30 Gallons","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8018,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"50 Gallons","answerDisplayText":"50 Gallons","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8019,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"40 Gallons","answerDisplayText":"40 Gallons","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8020,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8017,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"30 Gallons","answerDisplayText":"30 Gallons","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8018,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"50 Gallons","answerDisplayText":"50 Gallons","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8019,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"40 Gallons","answerDisplayText":"40 Gallons","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8020,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40359/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40359,"taskName":"Solar Water Heater System - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair a Solar Water Heater System","xmTaskDescriptor":"Solar Water Heater Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":264,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Solar Heater Water system thermosiphon","textMessagingName":"Svc Solar Water Htr","rolloverLongDesc":"Done by solar specialists. Heating systems collect solar energy \u0026 use it to heat a fluid which is then circulated throughout the building.","rolloverShortDesc":"Solar hot water systems.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair a Solar Water Heater System. HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened solar water heater repair contractors in your area.","htmlTitle":"Solar Water Heater Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":102,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Solar Water Heater System Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Solar Water Heater System - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Solar Water Heating Project","urlName":"Solar-Water-Heater-Repair-or-Service","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Solar Water Heater Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Solar,Heater,Water,system,thermosiphon,indirect","emcCategoryOid":-14820,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":653,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}